<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Project Portfolio on Francisco Rodrigues</title>
    <link>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Project Portfolio on Francisco Rodrigues</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Master&#39;s Thesis</title>
      <link>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>The baseline concept of aeroelastic tailoring is to gain control over the in-flight deformation of a lifting surface to manipulate the generation of external aerodynamic loads, to improve the overall aircraft performance. Active and passive technologies have been significantly studied to evaluate the benefits of the aeroelastic methodologies. However, the implementation of passive aeroelastic tailoring methods in helicopter design is significantly understudied. In this thesis is intended to study the aeroelastic behavior of an elastic rotor blade model during flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Recently graduated with a Master’s degree in Mechanical Engineering from Instituto Superior Técnico, having 5+ years of experience in programming, CAD modelling and Finite Element Analysis (FEA), with a further specialization in Machine Learning. Currently working on a Data Science Portfolio to gain hands-on experience by addressing real-world problems using advanced procedures of data analysis and visualization, and machine learning algorithms, including feature engineering, model training and evaluation, and fine-tuning and optimization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to contact me regarding any interest in my work. Hope to hear from you soon!
Phone: (+135) 911123184 Email: franrod98@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/fcmrodrigues </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Fake News Detection Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
