<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Francisco Rodrigues</title>
    <link>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Francisco Rodrigues</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Master&#39;s Thesis</title>
      <link>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>The baseline concept of aeroelastic tailoring is to gain control over the in-flight deformation of a lifting surface to manipulate the generation of external aerodynamic loads, to improve the overall aircraft performance. Active and passive technologies have been significantly studied to evaluate the benefits of the aeroelastic methodologies. However, the implementation of passive aeroelastic tailoring methods in helicopter design is significantly understudied. In this thesis is intended to study the aeroelastic behavior of an elastic rotor blade model during flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Fake News Detection Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://franrod98.github.io/FR_Porfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>Download the dataset: Visit the provided link and download the Fake.csv and True.csv files.
Explore the dataset: Load the CSV files into your data analysis environment (e.g., Python with pandas). Examine the columns, data types, and overall structure of the data.
Preprocess the data: Perform any necessary data preprocessing steps, such as removing duplicates, handling missing values, or cleaning the text content. Consider applying NLP techniques like tokenization, stopword removal, and stemming or lemmatization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
